Anderson, Marilyn and Jonathan Garlock "Rochester: A Community of Workers" Exhibit Materials 6331
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Marilyn Anderson and Jonathan Garlock "Rochester: A Community of Workers" Exhibit Materials
2011
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Anderson, Marilyn
Garlock, Jonathan
6331
11.67 cubic feet
11.3 linear ft.
Records.
7543506
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 12, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 01, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Anderson, Marilyn; Garlock, Jonathan; AFSCME. Council 2419; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Local 14 (Rochester, N.Y.); Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Local 205; Amalgamated Transit Union. Local 282; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists. Local 223; American Postal Workers Union. Local 215; Bricklayers' and Masons' International Union of America. Local 1134; Civil Service Employees Association (N.Y.). Local 828; Graphic Communications International Union. Local 38; Hotel Employees, Restaurant Employees & Nursing Home Organized Workers Local 466; International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada. Local 253; International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada. Local B-90; International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada. Local 25; International Association of Fire Fighters. Local 1071; International Association of Machinists. Local 1868; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers. Local 86; International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 118; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers. Local 509; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers. Local 323; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers. Local 381; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Local 1097; National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians. Local 22; National Association of Letter Carriers (U.S.). Local 210; New York State Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO. Local 283 (Rochester, N.Y.); New York State United Teachers. Local 2969; Service Employees International Union. Local 1199 (New York, N.Y.); Service Employees International Union. Local 222; United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry. Local 13; United Food and Commercial Workers International Union. Local 1
7543506
- Supplemental Negatives, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Several Negative Films
- Website Exhibit Pages, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Returning Photos to Workers (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Exhibit in the Community and in the Schools, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Several Photographs
- Exhibit Panels (Layout-design) - Artists' Statement (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Exhibit Text (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Exhibit Text Drafts (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Tape Transcription Totes (from Worksite Interviews), etc. Notes (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Airport Exhibits, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Airport Exhibits (B), 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Rochester - Union fliers, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Jon Garlock Scans (Exhibit text) Jon Garlock (pgs. 38-42 Exhibit text) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  2 floppy disks
- Supplemental Shoots -(27-39) Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Initial Shoots - (1)-(26) Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Negatives galore
- Shoot (1) IUE/DELCO, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  10 or more Photographs
- Shoot(2) PEF/Psych Ctr, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Negatives
- Shoot (3) IATSE/Cinema, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  4 Photographs and Negatives
- Shoot (4) GCIU/Heindl (Box 2, Folder 4)
  5 Photographs
- Shoot (5) IUE/GRS (Box 2, Folder 5)
  11 Photographs Negatives
- Shoot (6) (5) Laborers/ Sewer Tunnel Supplemental - Photos - No Text, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Shoots (7,8) 4 10 Trades/CAN, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Negatives, and 15 regular Photographs
- Shoot (9) 1199/Strong HOSP, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  10 Photographs
- Shoots (10,21) AFM, IATSE/RPO, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Negatives, and 8 Photographs
- Shoot (11) Here/ Conn. Ctr, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Shoot (12) SEIU/OTB, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Negatives, and 2 Photographs
- Shoot (13) IAFF, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Negatives, and 6 Photographs
- Shoot (14) ATU/RTS, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  Negatives, and 4 Photographs
- Shoot (15) NABET/CHIO, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  1 Photograph
- Shoot (16) 15 21 Painters/CLINTON Sq., 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Shoot (17) IAM/Davenport, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  Negatives, and 11 Photographs
- Shoot (18) UFCW/TOPS, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Shoot (19) APWU/USPS 18, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  Negatives, and 10 Photographs
- Shoot (20) AFSCME/RCSD, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Negatives, and 2 Photograph
- Shoot (22) ACTWU/H-F 17, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Negatives, and 9 Photographs
- Shoot (23) 9 IATSE/Redwings, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  Negatives and 1 Photograph
- Shoot (24) Guild/Gannett, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  Negatives, and 3 Photographs
- Shoot (25) 19 NYSUT/R-H (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Shoot (26) Now/Wesley, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  Negatives, and 7 Photographs
- Shoot (27) amp; (27-a), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Shoots (28), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  Negatives, and about 30 Photographs
- Shoot (29), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Shoots (30) (31), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Negatives and 14 Photographs
- Shoot (32), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Shoots (33) (34), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  Negatives, and 17 Photographs
- Shoot (35), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Shoot (36), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Shoot (37), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  Negatives, and 5 Photographs
- Shoot (38), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Shoot (39), 1993 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Can of Worms Project (Perini) (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Mt. Hope Sewer Tunnel System (GC F) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  2 Photograph
- Heindl Printers (Box 4, Folder 3)
- International Union of Electric, Electrical, Salaried Machine Furniture Workers, Local 509/ Delco Products Division (Box 4, Folder 4)
  3 Photographs
- Public Employees Federation, Local 283/ Rochester Psychiatric Center (Box 4, Folder 5)
  2 Photographs
- International Association of Theatrical Stage Employees, Local 253/ Pittsford Plaza Cinema (Box 4, Folder 6)
- International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried Machine Furniture Workers, Local 323 General Railway Signal Company (Box 4, Folder 7)
  4 Photographs
- Photos of Construction Workers (Box 4, Folder 8)
  9 Photographs
- National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians, Local 22; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, Local 223/WHEC TV-10 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 282/ Regional Transit System (Box 5, Folder 2)
- International Association of Firefighters, Local 1071/ City of Rochester (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Service Employees International Union, Local 222/ Off-Track Betting (Box 5, Folder 4)
- American Federation of Musicians. Local 66; International Association of Theatrical Stage Employees, Local 25/ Rochester Philharmonic Orchestra (Box 5, Folder 5)
- 1199 Rochester Hospital and Healthcare Employees Unions SEIU/ Strong Memorial Hospital (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Hotel Employees, Restaurant Employees Nursing - Home Organized Workers, Local 466/ Rochester Riverside Convention Center (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers, Locals 14 205/ Hickey Freeman (Box 6, Folder 1)
- American Postal Workers Union, Local 215/ U.S. Postal Service, General Mail Facility (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Board of Education Non-Teaching Employees, American Federation of State, County Municipal Employees, Local 2419/ Rochester City School District (Box 6, Folder 3)
- International Association of Machinists, Local 1868/ Davenport Machine (Box 6, Folder 4)
- United Food Commercial Workers, District 1/ Tops Friendly Markets (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Clinton Square Project (Le Cesse) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  6 Photographs
- New York State United Teachers, Local 2969/ Rush Henrietta School District (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Photographs of Machinery Workers (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Hotel Employees, Restaurant Employees Nursing-Home Organized Workers, Local 466/ Wesley-on-East (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Guild, Local 17; Graphic Communications International Union Local 503/Gannett Rochester Publishers (Box 7, Folder 4)
  7 Photographs
- International Association of Theatrical and Stage Employees, Local B-90 /Silver Stadium (Box 7, Folder 5)
- 'Speaking Out', 1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Photographers of Workers (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Photographers of Workers (Box 8, Folder 3)
- "Rochester 'A Community That Works'" and Several Large Photographers, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Over 20 Large Photographers
- Rochester Labor Council AFL-CIO 1993 Calendar (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Pages for Coloring (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Coloring Books (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Coloring Boards (Box 9, Folder 4)
- "Rochester: A Community of Workers" Photographs (Box 10, Folder 1)
- "Rochester: A Community of Workers" Photographs (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Plumbers 13, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Cassettes
- RCW1 5/11/90 -DELCO, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Cassette
- RCW2 Pex RPC 5/25/90, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- RCW22 RPO 8/25/90, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- RCW23 ACTWU Hickey-Freeman 8/27, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- RCW24 8/27 ACTWU Hickey Freeman 2, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- RCW 25 8/27/90 EASTEB-90 Silver, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- RCW26 8/31/90 Guild 17, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- RCW3 5/31/90 IATSE 253, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Firefighters 7/27 RCW 13, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- OTB RCW 12, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Here+ NTW RCW11, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- RCW10 7/21 RPO, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- RCW18 IAM 1868 Davenport 8/10/90, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- RCW19 UFCW TOPS 8/16/90, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- APWU 8/20/90 RCW20, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- RCW5 6/29/90 IUE 323 -GRS, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- RCW 4 GCIU/ Heindl, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- RCW 1199 -Strong 7/17/90, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- RCW 21 Bente- 8/20/90 AFSCME, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- IBEW Lo 86 5/26/93, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- NALC 210 5/19/93 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- PEF 5/4/01, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Bricklayers Local 11 5/17/93, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- IUE 381 11/2/92, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- 10/3/91 CSEA -LILACS, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- RCW 91/1 8/2 Airport2 Canal Bridge, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Airport Shoot 8/2/91 1, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- RCW 28 Here+Now 9/7/90 Wesley, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- RCW 27 9/7/90 NYSUT, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- RCW17 Construction Trades 8/6/90 Can/Clinton SQ, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- RCW16 Nabet 22 8/3/90, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- RCW15 ATV 282 2, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- APWU 5/7/01, 2001 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- UAW/AC 10/30/92, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- UAW 9/4/92, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- UPS 10/23/92, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Schlegel/ACTWU 3-T 8/18/92, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- RCW14 ATU 282 1 8/13/90, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- RCW 8 CAW 7/20, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- RCW7 7/14/90 Can- Concrete Pouring, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- 7/13 Laborers ACW 6, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 1)